[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "What are you looking at?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "looking", "at", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Not yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Dr. Oz, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Dr.", "Oz", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Very, very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", ",", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "What is the best advice for people to get to January and think New Year, new me, new start?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "best", "advice", "for", "people", "to", "get", "to", "January", "and", "think", "New", "Year", ",", "new", "me", ",", "new", "start", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, resolutions actually do make a difference.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "resolutions", "actually", "do", "make", "a", "difference", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "What are the things about the American diet, the way of life, whatever it may be, that are particular, perhaps, to America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "things", "about", "the", "American", "diet", ",", "the", "way", "of", "life", ",", "whatever", "it", "may", "be", ",", "that", "are", "particular", ",", "perhaps", ",", "to", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, we have made it easy to do the wrong thing in America.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "have", "made", "it", "easy", "to", "do", "the", "wrong", "thing", "in", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Just from French fries?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "from", "French", "fries", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Just from French fries.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "from", "French", "fries", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "RBR", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "If everybody just exercised better portion control, literally cut the amount they ate by, say, a third, what effect would that have on the average life?", "question_tokens": ["If", "everybody", "just", "exercised", "better", "portion", "control", ",", "literally", "cut", "the", "amount", "they", "ate", "by", ",", "say", ",", "a", "third", ",", "what", "effect", "would", "that", "have", "on", "the", "average", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WP", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "It would dramatically change our life expectancy, but, more importantly, the quality of our life.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "dramatically", "change", "our", "life", "expectancy", ",", "but", ",", "more", "importantly", ",", "the", "quality", "of", "our", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Is it good for America that you have a first lady and president who are obviously very physically fit themselves?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "good", "for", "America", "that", "you", "have", "a", "first", "lady", "and", "president", "who", "are", "obviously", "very", "physically", "fit", "themselves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "It's a huge benefit for the country.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "huge", "benefit", "for", "the", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "If you walked as an adult for half an hour a day -- you know, I walk here across Central Park, say, to CNN, and I feel like it's a pretty good exercise if you walk at a reasonable pace, is that enough to be fit?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "walked", "as", "an", "adult", "for", "half", "an", "hour", "a", "day", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "walk", "here", "across", "Central", "Park", ",", "say", ",", "to", "CNN", ",", "and", "I", "feel", "like", "it", "'s", "a", "pretty", "good", "exercise", "if", "you", "walk", "at", "a", "reasonable", "pace", ",", "is", "that", "enough", "to", "be", "fit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "TO", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "It's a perfect amount.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "perfect", "amount", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"], "LOCATION": ["Central Park"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Well, I'm basically in perfect physical (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "basically", "in", "perfect", "physical", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, we're going to --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Why do you think you've had a -- a battle with your weight?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ve", "had", "a", "--", "a", "battle", "with", "your", "weight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "If I could figure it out, I'd fix it.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "figure", "it", "out", ",", "I", "'d", "fix", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "You don't know what it is?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Did you ever get help for it?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "get", "help", "for", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Sure, plenty of times.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "plenty", "of", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Where do you -- where do you fall down in terms of dealing with it?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "--", "where", "do", "you", "fall", "down", "in", "terms", "of", "dealing", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "I eat too much.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "eat", "too", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Should they have the jab?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "they", "have", "the", "jab", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "I think they should have the -- the flu shot, without question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "should", "have", "the", "--", "the", "flu", "shot", ",", "without", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "What is the best advice, if there is any, for people who get caught up in these terrible tragedies, about how to somehow get back?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "best", "advice", ",", "if", "there", "is", "any", ",", "for", "people", "who", "get", "caught", "up", "in", "these", "terrible", "tragedies", ",", "about", "how", "to", "somehow", "get", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "What we ought to, I think, crave, is hope.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "we", "ought", "to", ",", "I", "think", ",", "crave", ",", "is", "hope", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "How do you deal with that particular kind of stress, a really -- like a death in the family, a death of a close friend, even, for some people, a death of a beloved pet?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "that", "particular", "kind", "of", "stress", ",", "a", "really", "--", "like", "a", "death", "in", "the", "family", ",", "a", "death", "of", "a", "close", "friend", ",", "even", ",", "for", "some", "people", ",", "a", "death", "of", "a", "beloved", "pet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Because I can't tell you how many times we've lost one couple, a long married couple, and then soon after, we'll lose the spouse.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "ca", "n't", "tell", "you", "how", "many", "times", "we", "'ve", "lost", "one", "couple", ",", "a", "long", "married", "couple", ",", "and", "then", "soon", "after", ",", "we", "'ll", "lose", "the", "spouse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Does that -- does it exist in medical terms, a broken heart?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "--", "does", "it", "exist", "in", "medical", "terms", ",", "a", "broken", "heart", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "There is no question at all that broken hearts exist and they kill people.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "no", "question", "at", "all", "that", "broken", "hearts", "exist", "and", "they", "kill", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Rhodiola?", "question_tokens": ["Rhodiola", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Rhodiola.", "answer_tokens": ["Rhodiola", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Are you basically telling me you've been half cut on vodka your entire career?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "basically", "telling", "me", "you", "'ve", "been", "half", "cut", "on", "vodka", "your", "entire", "career", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Can we add a few, you know, cannabis joints to the equation now that they're legal in some states?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "add", "a", "few", ",", "you", "know", ",", "cannabis", "joints", "to", "the", "equation", "now", "that", "they", "'re", "legal", "in", "some", "states", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Cannabis, a fascinating story, in part because there is no question there's medicinal benefit.", "answer_tokens": ["Cannabis", ",", "a", "fascinating", "story", ",", "in", "part", "because", "there", "is", "no", "question", "there", "'s", "medicinal", "benefit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "ORGAN: How addictive is cannabis?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "How", "addictive", "is", "cannabis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "It's addictive as cigarettes, in my opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "addictive", "as", "cigarettes", ",", "in", "my", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Is it more dangerous than cigarettes?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "more", "dangerous", "than", "cigarettes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "It does -- it has more dangers in part because when you're under the influence of cannabis, your judgment is a bit more affected than it would be under cigarettes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "--", "it", "has", "more", "dangers", "in", "part", "because", "when", "you", "'re", "under", "the", "influence", "of", "cannabis", ",", "your", "judgment", "is", "a", "bit", "more", "affected", "than", "it", "would", "be", "under", "cigarettes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "But if you, as one of America's topmost renowned doctors, says it's not more dangerous than cigarettes, surely, it should just be legalized, then, right, like cigarettes?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", ",", "as", "one", "of", "America", "'s", "topmost", "renowned", "doctors", ",", "says", "it", "'s", "not", "more", "dangerous", "than", "cigarettes", ",", "surely", ",", "it", "should", "just", "be", "legalized", ",", "then", ",", "right", ",", "like", "cigarettes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "There are a couple of problems with cannabis.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "a", "couple", "of", "problems", "with", "cannabis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "But how -- how bad is that, the mass index?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "--", "how", "bad", "is", "that", ",", "the", "mass", "index", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Well, the body mass index is -- it's in the overweight category, but I'm not that worried about that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "body", "mass", "index", "is", "--", "it", "'s", "in", "the", "overweight", "category", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "not", "that", "worried", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "What should my waist be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "my", "waist", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Half of your height, half of 73 inches, which is 36 and a half inches.", "answer_tokens": ["Half", "of", "your", "height", ",", "half", "of", "73", "inches", ",", "which", "is", "36", "and", "a", "half", "inches", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "How bad is that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "bad", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Well, ideally it would be less than 140.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "ideally", "it", "would", "be", "less", "than", "140", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What's mine?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "mine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Thirty-seven.", "answer_tokens": ["Thirty-seven", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "I need more healthy cholesterol -- how do I get more healthy cholesterol?", "question_tokens": ["I", "need", "more", "healthy", "cholesterol", "--", "how", "do", "I", "get", "more", "healthy", "cholesterol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "The best way to do it is to get that waist size down to 36 and a half inches.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "way", "to", "do", "it", "is", "to", "get", "that", "waist", "size", "down", "to", "36", "and", "a", "half", "inches", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "What's the best way to do that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "best", "way", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Uh, there are a couple of little tips.", "answer_tokens": ["Uh", ",", "there", "are", "a", "couple", "of", "little", "tips", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "But can I share that for a second?", "question_tokens": ["But", "can", "I", "share", "that", "for", "a", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "How high?", "question_tokens": ["How", "high", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "It's supposed to be, ideally, about 115 over 75, ideally.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "supposed", "to", "be", ",", "ideally", ",", "about", "115", "over", "75", ",", "ideally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "And what causes that kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "causes", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Z: Exercise.", "answer_tokens": ["Z", ":", "Exercise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", ":", "CC", "VBP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "So what should I be doing to deal with this?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "should", "I", "be", "doing", "to", "deal", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Well, the -- the number one thing that folks ought to start doing is to automate their lives so the easy decisions are the right ones and are -- and are easier to make.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "--", "the", "number", "one", "thing", "that", "folks", "ought", "to", "start", "doing", "is", "to", "automate", "their", "lives", "so", "the", "easy", "decisions", "are", "the", "right", "ones", "and", "are", "--", "and", "are", "easier", "to", "make", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Is that bad for me?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "bad", "for", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Coffee itself is fine, because it's a -- it's the number one source of antioxidants in America.", "answer_tokens": ["Coffee", "itself", "is", "fine", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "a", "--", "it", "'s", "the", "number", "one", "source", "of", "antioxidants", "in", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "-- I'm going to get you back in -- how -- how long would I need to try and really deal with this?", "question_tokens": ["--", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "get", "you", "back", "in", "--", "how", "--", "how", "long", "would", "I", "need", "to", "try", "and", "really", "deal", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", ":", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "You could dramatically change these numbers in six weeks.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "could", "dramatically", "change", "these", "numbers", "in", "six", "weeks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Or is it just luck?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "just", "luck", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Well, it's -- it's a combination.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "combination", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "So my question to you is, is there a preventative measure that I could use to help alleviate the pain so that, long-term, it won't turn into arthritis?", "question_tokens": ["So", "my", "question", "to", "you", "is", ",", "is", "there", "a", "preventative", "measure", "that", "I", "could", "use", "to", "help", "alleviate", "the", "pain", "so", "that", ",", "long-term", ",", "it", "wo", "n't", "turn", "into", "arthritis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "That's a great question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "What is the best way to try and deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "best", "way", "to", "try", "and", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "You know, we tackle this on the show a lot because there's actually 116 million Americans with chronic pain issues.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "tackle", "this", "on", "the", "show", "a", "lot", "because", "there", "'s", "actually", "116", "million", "Americans", "with", "chronic", "pain", "issues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "And what's the balance between genetics and just good living?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "'s", "the", "balance", "between", "genetics", "and", "just", "good", "living", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "It turns out that about two thirds of how long you live is based on your lifestyle.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "turns", "out", "that", "about", "two", "thirds", "of", "how", "long", "you", "live", "is", "based", "on", "your", "lifestyle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "What is the secret to long life, do you think, in terms of health?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "secret", "to", "long", "life", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "health", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "Good diet.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "diet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "Do what in bed?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "what", "in", "bed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "Mimi -- Mimi, let me ask you, have you ever some kind?", "question_tokens": ["Mimi", "--", "Mimi", ",", "let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "have", "you", "ever", "some", "kind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mimi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "Do you drink alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "drink", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "Milk.", "answer_tokens": ["Milk", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 787, "question": "What about that for a recipe for long life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "that", "for", "a", "recipe", "for", "long", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 788, "answer": "It's obviously worked.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "obviously", "worked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 811, "question": "And if you can't get enough, what do you do about it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "ca", "n't", "get", "enough", ",", "what", "do", "you", "do", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 812, "answer": "The -- the number one under appreciated health problem in America is sleep issues.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "--", "the", "number", "one", "under", "appreciated", "health", "problem", "in", "America", "is", "sleep", "issues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "It can't help you sleep, does it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "ca", "n't", "help", "you", "sleep", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "It -- it completely disrupts sleep patterns, and for one very important reason.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "--", "it", "completely", "disrupts", "sleep", "patterns", ",", "and", "for", "one", "very", "important", "reason", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 862, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 863, "answer": "You cannot get the flu from the flu shot because the material is -- is actually dead flu virus.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "not", "get", "the", "flu", "from", "the", "flu", "shot", "because", "the", "material", "is", "--", "is", "actually", "dead", "flu", "virus", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 873, "question": "You're enjoying this, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "enjoying", "this", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 874, "answer": "This is literally the biggest needle I could find.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "literally", "the", "biggest", "needle", "I", "could", "find", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 897, "question": "Should children have them?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "children", "have", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 898, "answer": "It's recommended that after the age of six months, that we give it to our kids.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "recommended", "that", "after", "the", "age", "of", "six", "months", ",", "that", "we", "give", "it", "to", "our", "kids", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 922, "question": "How much of it is mental in the end?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "it", "is", "mental", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 923, "answer": "You know, mental is where you win it all.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "mental", "is", "where", "you", "win", "it", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]